https://hollandbowlmill.com/privacy-policy/

SAVE TODAY
Free shipping on orders $75 or more. Limited to standard ground shipping in the continental US.
$932.50
Cart
Privacy Policy
This Holland Bowl Mill privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for hollandbowlmill.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website. It will notify you of the following:What personally identifiable information is obtained from you through the site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. Information Collection, Use, and SharingHolland Bowl Mill is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/ receive information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contacts from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g., to ship an order.Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.Your Access to and Control Over InformationYou may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address, or phone number is given on our website:See what data we have about you if any.Change/correct any data we have about you.Have us delete any data we have about you.Express any concern you have about our use of your data. SecurityWe take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and securely transmitted to us. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or search for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. Updates to Privacy PolicyWe may make updates to this Privacy Policy periodically without notification. Please refer to this policy when necessary to check for updates.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via telephone at (616) 396-6513 or via email.
Lifetime Guarantee on all Wooden Bowls
All Holland Bowl Mill bowls come with a lifetime guarantee. If your bowl ever cracks or warps from regular use, Holland Bowl Mill will replace it with a new one of similar size and finish. Never let water stand in a wood bowl for a long period of time and never clean wood bowls or any wood product in the dishwasher. Holland Bowl Mill recommends using water and a small amount of mild soap to clean your wood products, then hand dry.Holland Bowl Mill accepts payment by Visa, MasterCard, American Express and Discover credit cards and through PayPal. You may place your order through our secure online shopping cart, by phone at (616) 396-6513 or by fax at (616) 396-0642.Artists and retailers please contact us at (616) 396-6513 for information on wholesale pricing!
Contact
Holland Bowl Mill120 James StreetHolland, MI 49424-1824
Phone: (616) 396-6513
Fax: (616) 396-0642
Email
Retail/Showroom Hours
Monday-Friday: 9:00am-5:00pm
Saturday: 10:00am-4:00pm
Sunday: Closed
Free Tours Of The Mill
Monday-Friday:9:00am-12:00pm & 12:30pm-3:00pm
No appointment needed if group is under 10.For larger groups, call 616-396-6513 to schedule your tour.
Follow Holland Bowl Mill
Facebook
Instagram
Youtube
Rss
All information collected on this site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold, reused, rented, disclosed, or loaned. Any information given to the Holland Bowl Mill or any of its employees will be used only in ways that have been specifically consented to by the customer. If you have any questions, please feel free to call or email us.
FAQ
Product Care
Custom Engraving
Wholesale
Showroom
About Us
Blog
Refunds and Exchanges
© 2020 Holland Bowl Mill
We can no longer guarantee Christmas Delivery!Please allow 10-14 business days for orders to ship. If you do need an order sooner, please choose expedited shipping at checkout (expedited shipping does not guarantee CHRISTMAS DELIVERY.)
We greatly appreciate all orders during these trying times, please email us at hbm@hollandbowlmill.com with any questions or concerns. Stay safe and healthy! HBM Team.
x
